http://lisaa6.sg-host.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy -
Skip to navigation
Skip to content
Search for:
Privacy Policy
This privacy policy discloses the privacy practices for Antech Wire EDM Inc.
Information We Collect, The Use, and Sharing
We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site and will not share it with anyone. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone.
We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third-party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request, e.g. to ship an order.
Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy.
Your Access to and Control Over Information
You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us via the email address or phone number given on our website.
Security
We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline.
While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information.
Updates
Our Privacy Policy may change from time to time and all updates will be posted on this page.
If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately via telephone at (905) 435 – 0633 or via email: antechwire@gmail.com
Search for:
Hours & Info330 Marwood Drive
Unit #6 & 7
Oshawa, Ontario
L1H 8B4 (905) 435 0633antech2@gmail.comMonday: 8am-5pm
Tuesday: 8am-5pm
Wednesday: 8am-5pm
Thursday: 8am-5pm
Friday: 8am-5pm
Saturday: CLOSED
Sunday: CLOSED
Recent Posts
Clutch Disk!
CAD Drawings!
The History of Toronto Spanning over 300 Years!
Header Gaskets!
New Metal Art Designs!
Recent CommentsArchives
February 2017
January 2017
December 2016
November 2016
October 2016
September 2016
August 2016
WordPress.org
WE ACCEPT:
© Antech Wire EDM Inc. 2017330 Marwood Dr. Unit 6&7 Oshawa, ON  L1H 8B4  CanadaPrecision Wire EDM and WaterJet Cutting in Oshawa, ON CanadaTEL: (905) 435 – 0633  FAX: (905) 435 – 2097
©
2020						 Storefront designed by WooCommerce.
My Account
Search
Search for:
Search
0
